myfriendsfeet.com 2004-12-04

# 

WebRing is concerned about your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**NOTICE:[Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee/index.html) for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission.**

This Privacy Policy covers WebRing's treatment of personal information that WebRing collects when you use the WebRing site, and when you use WebRing's services. This policy also covers WebRing's treatment of any personal information that WebRing's business partners share with WebRing or that WebRing may collect on a partner's site. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that WebRing does not own or control, or to people that WebRing does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**  

  * WebRing collects personal information when you register for a WebRing account, when you use WebRing products or services, when you visit WebRing pages. WebRing may also receive personal information from our business partners. 
  * When you register with WebRing, we ask for your email address and birth date. Once you register with WebRing and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * WebRing also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser WebRing cookie information and the page you requested. 
  * WebRing uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to provide traffic statistics to our RingMasters. None of the statistics reported include personal information about any WebRing user. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  

  * WebRing will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. 
  * WebRing may send personal information about you to other companies or people when: 
    * We have your consent to share the information; 
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 
    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of WebRing to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personal information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.); 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or 
    * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the WebRing Terms of Service, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**Cookies**  

  * WebRing may set and access WebRing cookies on your computer. 
  * WebRing allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to WebRing's cookies. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**  

  * WebRing gives you the ability to edit your WebRing Account Information and preferences at any time. 

**Security**  

  * Your WebRing Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

  * WebRing may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
